I wonder if I should have never met him in the first place.
Of course.
But I still would have.
Well, now, I only know the new song Last Roth
I can't stop even though I know it's no good
It's a song that expresses the feelings of love
So, I would like to ask all the members
I can't stop even though I know it's no good
I'd like you to announce your sweet and dangerous love
I would like you to announce your sweet and dangerous favorite things.
First of all, let's ask Mr. Otani to announce his sweet and dangerous favorite thing.
Mr. Otani, let's have you announce your sweet and dangerous favorite thing.
Mr. Otani, please!
I wonder if I should have never met him in the first place.
But still, I...
I like more garlic.
What does this mean?
I love jiro-type ramen
I love Jiro's ramen, especially with garlic toppings.
I put a little bit of garlic on my ramen, as some of you do, too.
But when I put it on myself, I like to have a little bit of garlic.
That's great!
That much?
You put that much on?
Are you okay with it the next day?
I'm fine.
The music video for "Tell me what you like about me"...
There was a dance scene in the morning.
And then there was a break before the drama scene.
I went to eat ramen during that time.
I eat a lot of garlic.
Are you okay today?
No, I'm fine today.
Are you okay?
Is it okay if I stop?
I'm fine.
It's all right.
There might be. Have the members noticed?
Not at all.
Good. Let's continue. Mr. Takamatsu, please.
It's sweet and dangerous.
I wish we'd never met. I still like to go to convenience stores and buy things.
I do. Do you do?
Yes, I do... but only once every three months.
Yes, when I've finished an important singing show or a big job, I go to the famous Suntempo, right?
I go around there. What do you buy?
Everything. Like crazy.
Ice cream. What do you recommend?
I recommend... I recommend... I'm glad you recommend it.
I recommend the frozen noodles from the green store. They're really good.
I don't want to eat it.
I'll buy some and eat it at home. After a big show, we usually go to a convenience store, right?
I eat a lot. I buy about 10,000 yen worth.
10,000 yen worth? You're a YouTube star!
I buy it in an eco-friendly bag. That's good.
I'll bring my own bag.
I'll go all out. I'll buy a lot of stuff.
I can't stop. It feels good.
It's refreshing.
Let's go to Mr. Akiwaki.
Please do something sweet and vague.
I wish we'd never met. I still like UFO catchers.
It's cute.
It's cute. What do you think?
I'm basically a candy taker.
Heh.
Hitomi and I went UFO-catching for stuffed animals the other day.
But we couldn't get the stuffed animal.
I've been doing it all my life, and I'm in danger of losing my wallet.
Oh no!
And nowadays, you can use your credit card.
Paintings...
I've got a history of emails between the two of us, but it's just a history of using the card.
I stopped when there was no history.
So you notice.
I thought it was a bad idea, but I thought if I did it one more time, I could get it.
That's why I decided to limit myself to sweets.
I feel a great sense of accomplishment because I can catch sweets.
You can get the sweets?
The stuffed animals were a little difficult.
It's so difficult.
I use it after only one piece.
You mean? I think it was a bad day.
You didn't get it? I didn't get it.
It's such a shame. But it feels good, doesn't it?
It's great when you get it.
Let's continue with Ms. Sasaki... who likes abalone.
I wish we'd never met. I still prefer the salt.
I worry about everything. I worry about myself too.
Eat it as it is. Eat the salt as it is.
How did you get it in your hand? Like that.
Aradio? Aradio, whatever.
When do you eat it? When I'm hungry. Like a snack.
For a long time, salt and tea, like a snack.
Yes.
I used to alternate between the two, but people were worried about my health.
I'm sorry, it's a little sweet or a little salty.
I have to be careful.
Let's continue with Saito Kiyohara-san's sweet and salty favorite.
I wish we'd never met. Still...
I like to pick up my plate at the sushi bar.
Isn't it cute? What's this?
I love sushi conveyor belts. I often go there. At first, I was excited.
But as the sushi started to flow...
Sushi?
I don't like it when the sushi stops. I want to get it as soon as possible.
I wanted to take the sushi as soon as it came out of the machine.
You take the sushi while it's still flowing? It's a matter of whether it stops or not.
If you stop, you lose.
You're going it alone, right?
Who are you fighting?
Just one guy.
That was really good.
That's one of the things I love about sushi.
It's Chiara World.
It's a sport. Sushi cart sports.
I want to monitor it sometime.
That sounds fun.
I'd like to try it.
I want to see how fast you can do it.
I want you to try it. Go check it out.
It's even better.
I see. So we can eat it faster.
The sooner we eat it, the fresher it'll be.
Last but not least, Mr. Noguchi.
I wonder if I should have never met you.
But still... I like to eat a cup of noodles and go to bed right away.
I like to eat a cup of noodles and go to bed right away.
That sounds better.
Eating and sleeping is the best for you, right?
It's good.
And late at night. Late at night.
It's around midnight, when I should be in bed.
I thought I'd have a cup of ramen.
It's gluten, so it raises your blood sugar.
It makes you sleepy.
Sleeping in that sleepy state is the best feeling.
That's right. Blood is good.
If you can't sleep, you should eat.
It's better to eat.
So if you're having trouble sleeping lately, by all means, have a bowl of noodles.
So you always keep at least one cup of noodles in the kitchen?
Sometimes I don't know what to eat if I don't have one.
You have a huge stock.
I have a huge stock.
I have some, but lately I'm starting to think it's not good for me, so I'm trying my best.
I had some yesterday.
I had a double.
Daimama?
You do that at home?
You do damedama at home?
Cup ramen. I like cup ramen with noodles.
I like to eat udon noodles afterwards.
Yesterday, I had some Chinese noodles.
I boiled them and put them in the bowl and ate them.
It was delicious.
I went to bed.
I went to bed
As soon as I went to bed
Don't worry a bit.
You're young, and you're dancing.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
That's good.
It's getting dangerous, isn't it?
Thank you very much.